Guide to the Time Inc. Time Publishing and Business Records 1929-1999 MS 3009-RG 24
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Promotion and Public Affairs Department Records, 1955-1999; 155.1 Linear feet in 156 record cartons, 1 document case, and 2 flat boxes
  - Subseries IV.C. Public Affairs Manager Anne Janas Files, 1986-1992; 8 Linear feet in 8 record cartons
    - Subsubseries IV.C.3. Project Files, 1988-1992; 4 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: C-SPAN (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 13)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Edelman (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 14)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Education Week (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 15)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: 800 Number (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 16)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Fact Sheets (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 17)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Filler Ads (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 18)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: HBO Public Service Announcements (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 19)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Invitation (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 20)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Kirshner, Gloria (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 21)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Legal Challenge by Presidential Candidate (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 22)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Lerman, Jeannette (Time Warner Corporate Communications) (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 23)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Levin, Jerry Memorandum (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 24)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Logo (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 25)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Los Angeles (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 26)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Memoranda (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 27-29)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Model Releases [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R56)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: New York (Magazine) (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 30)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Newspapers in Education? Mailing (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 31)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Kids-Vote (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 32)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Op Ed (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 33)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Photographic Material (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 34)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Presentation (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 35)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Press List (Cooperating Organizations) (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 1)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Press Release (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 2)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Publisher's Letter (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 3)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Radio Public Service Announcements [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 4)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Results (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 5)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: The Roper Organization, Inc. (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 6)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Spanish Ballot (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 7)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Special Mailings (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 8)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: State Coordinators (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 9)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Student Interviews (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 10)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Teacher Guides (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 11)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Time/HBO Presentation (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 12)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Time Lines (Marketing Publication) (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 13)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Washington Letters (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 14)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Whittle Communications/Channel One (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 15)
      - Opinion Leader Mailings, 1989 (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 19)
  - Subseries IV.D. Publicity Manager Files, 1964-1970; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Jack Mulligan and Alex Burnham are not listed in the Time Inc. department head lists. According to correspondence to Jack Mulligan, he was appointed to the position of Time Publicity Manager in 1967. His sign off on the Early Edit Briefs indicates this position was part of Public Affairs. Based on the records, Alex Burnham took over as Publicity Manager in mid-1969.
    The Publicty Manager Files includes records from Jack Mulligan and Alex Burnham. Records include correspondence and memoranda with other Time Inc. departments such as Corporate Public Affairs and the Time publisher; and with heads of advertising from other companies. Correspondence and memoranda include material forwarded by the Director of Public Affairs for the Publicity Manager to handle. Mulligan's files contain some from his previous position at the marketing company Young & Rubicam including his service on a USIA task force.
    - "Behavior" Mailing, 1969 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 1)
    - Bills, 1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 2)
    - Broadcasting: "On the Air", 1969 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 3)
    - Broadcasting: Publicity, 1969 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 4)
    - Broadcasting: Other Companies, 1968 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 6-8)
    - Covers: Beatles, 1967 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 9-10)
    - Covers: Futures, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 11-12)
    - Covers: Rusk-Smith Wedding, 1967 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 13)
    - Current Affairs Test, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 14)
    - Curtis Circulation Company: Time National Distributor, 1969 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 15)
    - Drug Guide: Memoranda, 1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 16)
    - Drug Guide: Publicity, 1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 17)
    - Early Edit Brief, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 18-22)
      The Early Edit Brief is a advance abstract of the upcoming issue of Time sent out by the Publicity Manager for use by various other Time Inc. offices.
    - Essay Titles and Dates List, 1968? (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 23)
    - "Frequency": Time's Little Red College of Frequency Knowledge, 1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 24)
    - International Press Clip Reports, 1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 25)
    - Ithaca College, 1966 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 26)
    - Journalism Programs and Student Newspapers in Harlem, 1968 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 27)
    - Life on the Edit Side In-House Newsletter, 1967 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 28)
    - Life Publicity Releases, 1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 29)
    - Lists: Complimentary Circulation, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 30)
    - Magazine Industry Newsletter, 1969 (Offsite-box 2945, Folder 31)
    - Magazine Publishers Association, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 1-2)
    - Man of the Year, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 4-6)
    - Missing "I" Campaign, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 7)
    - Operation Intimate: Bandwagon Branch, 1969 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 8)
      A test of special distribution to metropolitan-area news media.
    - Publisher's Letter: Anti-War, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 9)
    - Publisher's Letter: The Beatles, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 10)
    - Publisher's Letter: Changes, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 11)
    - Publisher's Letter: College Ads, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 12)
    - Publisher's Letter: Effects of Time, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 13)
    - Publisher's Letter: Greenway, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 14)
    - Publisher's Letter: Hippies, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 15)
    - Publisher's Letter: Shah, 1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 16)
    - Time Audio, 1969 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 17)
      Proposal and exploration of an audio version of Time.
    - United States Information Agency (USIA), 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 18-20)
    - Young & Rubicam Telephone Directory, undated (Offsite-box 2946, Folder 21)
  - Subseries IV.E. Special Events Manager Jean C. Gussenhoven Files, 1997-1999; 7 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
    Jean "Nini" Gussenhoven's files contain her records on Time's 75th anniversary gala, planning for the canceled 1993 Executive News Conference, focusing on the incoming administration of President Bill Clinton, planning for Time Inc. staff and guests to attend the 1996 Summer Olympics in Atlanta for which Time International was a publishing sponsor, and the newstour CHINA 1999. Records on earlier anniversaries are in the Promotion and Public Affairs Department Records: Events Files. Materials on other newstours are in the Promotion and Public Affairs Department Records: Newstour Files. Additional files on CHINA 1999 are in Joelle Attinger's files in Time Editorial Records.
    - Events: Anniversaries: 75th, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 3121)
      The celebration for Time's 75th anniversary in 1998 was a gala at Radio City Music Hall including dinner, dancing, and tributes to past cover subjects by notable people including Toni Morrison, James Watson, Steven Spielberg, Mikhail Gorbachev, Bill Gates, Mary Tyler Moore, and Bill Clinton, including an Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater performance as a tribute to Duke Ellington.
      Records include correspondence with Radio City Music Hall, speakers, contractors, and consultants; the printed program; guest lists; invitations; logistics arrangements for guest accommodations and travel, budgets; production plans; and seating plans.
    - Events: Anniversaries: 75th, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 3122)
    - Events: Anniversaries: 75th, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 3123)
    - Events: Anniversaries: 75th, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 3124, Folder 1-14)
    - Events: Anniversaries: 75th [RESTRICTED], 1997-1998 (Offsite-box R56)
      Folder "Research Database" contains digital material of guests lists:
      5 computer discs (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in.
    - Events: Executive News Conference, 1989 (Offsite-box 3247, Folder 1)
    - Events: Executive News Conference, 1993 (Offsite-box 3247, Folder 2-52)
    - Events: 1996 Summer Olympics (Offsite-box 3248)
    - Events: 1996 Summer Olympics [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R56)
    - Newstour: CHINA 1999 (Offsite-box 3124, Folder 15-18)
      Locations visited during the China newstour were Beijing and a trip down the Yangtze River. Records include correspondence with the travel company Abercrombie & Kent; itineraries; participant lists and bios; and arrangements for transportation and accommodations.
    - Newstour: CHINA 1999 (Offsite-box 3125)
  - Subseries IV.F. Promotion Manager Nancy Hall Megan Files, 1957-1983; 12.67 Linear feet in 12 record cartons
    Early files name her as Nancy Hall until she marries in the late 1960s and becomes Nancy Megan. As early as 1969, Megan signs off as part of the Time public affairs department. In 1980, she signs as the manager of promotion operations. The Department Heads List includes her as the Promotion Manager from 1981 to 1984 and in 1985, she is called the Associate Promotion Director. By 1987, she is no longer listed as working at Time Inc.
    Nancy Hall Megan's files document her work on organizing promotional exhibitions featuring art owned by Time Inc., particularly Time cover art, and the revival of the advertising competition "Power of Print."
    Subsubseries III.F.1. Exhibition Files
    Subsubseries III.F.2. Office Files
    Subsubseries III.F.3. Project Files
    - Subsubseries IV.F.1. Exhibition Files, 1957-1983; 10.67 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
      Exhibition Files includes materials on exhibitions created by Time. Most of the exhibitions are shown at venues other than the Time & Life Building. The earlier files are from business manager John Keller, his assistant Ann Bellows, public affairs director Robert Sweeney, or are unspecified. Later files are from Time promotion and special events staff Nancy Hall Megan. A note from Bellows to Megan in a Boris Artzybasheff folder indicates Megan took possession of the earlier non-Cover Art files.
      The Time Cover Art Show files are primarily from Megan, quoted as "handling the cover show bookings for Time domestic," though files prior to 1967 are from Keller or Bellows. A note from Bellows to Megan indicates the tour files were kept by Megan although earlier files may have been created by Bellows.
      The Time Cover Art Show had several tour iterations grouped by year spans based on existing divider tabs. Iternations included subsets of tours so that each venue did not received the same collection of cover art. The title of the exhibition could change based on venue and the tours are rarely referred to by official titles. Repeated titles used include Cover Artists and Contemporary Portraiture from the Covers of Time.
      "Loans from" in the 1968-1970 tour include records on cover show items lent to other exhibitions or limited versions of the Time Cover Art Show which are not considered part of an official touring show. Cover art loan files from other years were included among the tour grouping at the time the loan occurred even if the loan was not related to the touring show.
      Records in the Individual Shows sometimes state one is similar to another one or reference an exhibition in Chicago on the Ad Age, but it does not look like these are all part of the same organized tour.
      Records include internal and external correspondence, catalogues, brochures, press releases, artwork inventories, photographs of exhibitions and related events, shipping invoices, and other related bills.
      - General: Catalogues, 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 1)
      - Alfred Eisenstaedt, Chicago, IL, 1967 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 2)
      - Boris Artzybasheff Memorial: General, 1965 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 3-5)
      - Boris Artzybasheff Memorial: Covers Borrowed from Subjects, 1965 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 6)
      - Boris Artzybasheff Memorial: Lists and Inventories, 1965 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 7-8)
      - Boris Artzybasheff Memorial: Preview Party, 1965 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 9-10)
      - Boris Artzybasheff Memorial: University Bequests, 1965 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 11)
      - Boris Chaliapin: El Paso Museum of Art, 1971 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 12a)
      - Britain 1923-1983: an American View Scrapbook (Offsite-box 2846, Folder 2)
        This exhibition was part of a celebration of Time's 60th anniversary.
      - Political Cover Show (canceled), 1968 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 12b)
      - Time Cover Art Donation, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3091, Folder 1-2)
      - Time Cover Art Donation [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R56)
      - Time Cover Art Show: General, 1968-1982 (Offsite-box 3091, Folder 3-18)
        Includes brochures, combined itinerary schedules, cover researcher Rosemary Frank's biography, contents of shows, lists of available works, crate and panel construction information, invitation samples, and notes on individual works.
      - Time Cover Art Show: General: Slides, circa 1967-circa 1971 (Offsite-box 3005, Folder 1)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: General (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 13)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Blurbs, 1963? (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 14)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Loans: Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 15)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Loans: David Stone Martin, 1966 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 16)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Loans: Fort Dodge Art Fair, 1966 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 17)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Loans: Philadelphia Museum of Art (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 18)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Loans: Vanderbilt University (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 19)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Requests to Show, 1963-1968 (Offsite-box 2856, Folder 20-21)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Atlanta Art Association, Atlanta, GA (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 1-2)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Akron Art Institute, Akron, OH, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 3)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Bullock's Downtown, Los Angeles, CA (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 4)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Cincinnati Art Museum, Cincinnati, OH (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 5)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, Colorado Springs, CO, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 6)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Dayton's Department Store, Minneapolis, MN (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 7)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Denver Art Museum, Denver, CO, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 8)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego, San Diego, CA, 1966 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 9)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: First National City Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 10-11)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: G. Fox and Co., Hartford, CT (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 12)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: George Sherman Union of Boston University, Boston, MA, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 13)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: The Hecht Co., Baltimore, MD (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 14)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: I. Magnin and Co., San Francisco, CA (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 15)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: J. B. Speed Art Museum, Louisville, KY, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 16)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Joslyn Art Museum, Omaha, NE, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 17)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: M. H. de Young Memorial Museum, San Francisco, CA, 1966 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 18-19)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Milwaukee Art Center, Milwaukee, WI (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 20)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Royal Ontario Museum, Toronto, ON, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 2857, Folder 21-22)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, Philadelphia, PA, 1963 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 1-2)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Salt Lake Art Center, Salt Lake City, UT (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 3)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Seattle Art Museum, Seattle, WA, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 4)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Tennessee Fine Arts Center, Nashville, TN, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 5)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Time & Life Reception Room, New York, NY (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 6)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Vancouver Art Gallery, Vancouver, BC, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 7)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Willistead Art Gallery, Windsor, ON, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 8)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1964-1967 Tour: Venues: Witte Memorial Museum, San Antonio, TX, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 9)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Brochures, 1967 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 10-11)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Early Correspondence with Branch Managers (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 12)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: European Show / FNCB (canceled) (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 13)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Loans From: Australia, 1969 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 14)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Loans From: Boston Public Library (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 15)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Loans From: Ottawa Art Center, 1969 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 16)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Loans From: Owens-Corning Fiberglas Exhibition Center (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 17)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Loans From: Park College (Missouri), 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 18)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Outside Requests (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 19)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Poster and Brochure Samples, 1964-1970 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 20)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Schedule (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 21)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Time Life International, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 2858, Folder 22)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Caterpillar Tractor Company, Peoria, IL (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 1)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Crown Zellerbach Corporation, San Francisco, CA, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 2)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Dayton Advertising Club, Dayton, OH, 1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 3)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Delaware Art Center, Wilmington, DE (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 4-5)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: El Paso Museum of Art, El Paso, TX, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 6)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Experiment in International Living, Putney, VT, 1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 7)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Expo '67, Montreal, QC, 1966 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 8)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Fifth International Salon of Cartoons, Montreal, QC (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 9)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: First Federal Savings and Loan Association of Chicago, Chicago, IL, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 10)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Grand Rapids Art Museum, Grand Rapids, MI, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 11-12)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Hemisfair, San Antonio, TX (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 13)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Indianapolis Museum of Art/The Herron Gallery, Indianapolis, IN, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 14)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Miami Press Club, Miami, FL, 1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 15)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Philbrook Art Center, Tulsa, OK (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 16)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Smith College, Northampton, MA (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 17)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: St. Paul Art Center, St. Paul, MN, 1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 18)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Webster College/Loretto Hilton Center, Webster Groves, MO, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 19)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Wichita Art Museum, Wichita, KS, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 20)
      - Time Cover Art Show: 1968-1970 Tour: Venues: Rejections (Offsite-box 2859, Folder 21)
      - Time Cover Art Show: National Portrait Gallery (Smithsonian Institution): Portraits of American Newsmakers, 1969 (Offsite-box 3005, Folder 2-18)
        This was the principal exhibition for the summer of 1969 at the National Portrait Gallery (NPG) shortly after the opening of the NPG. Time Inc. would donate its cover art collection to the NPG less than ten years later in 1978. Records include lists of art objects, correspondence, acceptances and regrets of invited cover subjects, invitations, catalogues, a poster, and reception photographs.
      - Time Cover Art Show: Portraits of a Dynamic Age, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 3091, Folder 19-33)